<quest id="2">
	<name>Sharptalon's Claw</name>
	<startedType>item</startedType>
	<startedBy>16305</startedBy>
	<finishedBy>12696</finishedBy>
	<level>20-30</level>
	<xp>3600</xp>
	<reputation>120</reputation>
	<decription>Bring Sharptalon's Claw to Senani Thunderheart at Splintertree Post, Ashenvale.</decription>
	<detail>The mighty hippogryph Sharptalon has been slain, with the claw of the felled beast serving as a testament to your victory. Senani Thunderheart at the Splintertree Post will no doubt be interested in seeing this trophy as proof of your deeds.</detail>
	<incomplete>Yes, mighty {class}, I sensed your arrival. I trust you have more news to report to me about your hunt?</incomplete>
	<completion>Most impressive, {name}... the claw of Sharptalon could not have been easy to get! The Ashenvale Hunt goes well for you!

	Sharptalon had long terrorized the peons from the lumber camps near its path as they tried to travel here to Splintertree Post. No doubt once the word gets out that it was you who put down the beast, many rousing songs of your bravery will be heard at campfires and lumber mills across Ashenvale!</completion>
	<questType>deliver</questType>
</quest>

<quest id="5">
	<name>Jitters' Growling Gut</name>
	<startedType>npc</startedType>
	<startedBy>288</startedBy>
	<finishedBy>272</finishedBy>
	<level>15-20</level>
	<xp>1786</xp>
	<reputation>80</reputation>
	<decription>Speak with Chef Grual.</decription>
	<detail>I've been stuck hiding in this ghost town for weeks, and I haven't eaten anything but grubs and weeds! I need some decent food, and I'm willing to trade well for it.$B$BBring me a feast and I'll pay you handsomely.$B$BI heard Chef Grual at the Scarlet Raven Tavern in Darkshire makes very good Dusky Crab Cakes...</detail>
	<incomplete>Oh, a shipment from my brother? Splendid! Fortune truly shines on me today!</incomplete>
	<completion>You need some Crab Cakes, do you? Well I might be able to cook some up for you...</completion>
	<questType>talkto</questType>
</quest>

<quest id="9061">
	<name>Cryptstalker Wristguards</name>
	<startedType>npc</startedType>
	<startedBy>16132</startedBy>
	<finishedBy>16132</finishedBy>
	<level>60</level>
	<decription>Huntsman Leopold at Light's Hope Chapel in the Eastern Plaguelands will make Cryptstalker Wristguards if you bring him the following: 1 Desecrated Wristguards, 6 Wartorn Chain Scraps, 1 Arcanite Bar and 2 Cured Rugged Hides.</decription>
	<detail>I've been stuck hiding in this ghost town for weeks, and I haven't eaten anything but grubs and weeds! I need some decent food, and I'm willing to trade well for it.$B$BBring me a feast and I'll pay you handsomely.$B$BI heard Chef Grual at the Scarlet Raven Tavern in Darkshire makes very good Dusky Crab Cakes...</detail>
	<incomplete>Oh, a shipment from my brother? Splendid! Fortune truly shines on me today!</incomplete>
	<completion>You need some Crab Cakes, do you? Well I might be able to cook some up for you...</completion>
	<questType>talkto</questType>
	<rewards>
		<item>22443</item>
	</rewards>
</quest>